mydiddle.com 2008-10-19

# Privacy Policy

**12** **May** **2008** Filed under: [Frm Admin](http://mydiddle.com/?cat=2601 "View all posts in Frm Admin")

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site MyDiddle.com . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Yahoo!), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: AdBrite etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Related topics:

  1. [India’s IT growth to fall on Western slowdown](http://mydiddle.com/?p=1294 "Permanent Link: India’s IT growth to fall on Western slowdown")
  2. [Thumbprint Cookies with Jam](http://mydiddle.com/?p=682 "Permanent Link: Thumbprint Cookies with Jam")
  3. [Write to me, I will reply: Amitabh Bachchan](http://mydiddle.com/?p=559 "Permanent Link: Write to me, I will reply: Amitabh Bachchan")
  4. [Disclaimer](http://mydiddle.com/?p=940 "Permanent Link: Disclaimer")
  5. [The Other Side of a Free Web Hosting Plan](http://mydiddle.com/?p=267 "Permanent Link: The Other Side of a Free Web Hosting Plan")
  6. [Know the Efficiency of Banner Advertising](http://mydiddle.com/?p=290 "Permanent Link: Know the Efficiency of Banner Advertising")
  7. [Encyclopedia Britannica Now Free For Bloggers](http://mydiddle.com/?p=601 "Permanent Link: Encyclopedia Britannica Now Free For Bloggers")
  8. [How to Be a Blogging Star](http://mydiddle.com/?p=178 "Permanent Link: How to Be a Blogging Star")
  9. [Bollywood Divides Over Imran-Harman](http://mydiddle.com/?p=1889 "Permanent Link: Bollywood Divides Over Imran-Harman")
  10. [Protect Your Laptop!](http://mydiddle.com/?p=3941 "Permanent Link: Protect Your Laptop!")
